Guide to the Women's and Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Movements (LGBT) Periodicals Collection, 1957-2017 RL.01399
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Women's and Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Movements (LGBT) periodicals collection
1957-2017
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture
RL.01399
63 Linear Feet
Since the 1960s, and particularly after the Stonewall uprising of 1969, the modern women's rights and lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender rights movements (LGBT) have produced their own magazines, journals, newspapers, and newsletters as a strategy for unifying and galvanizing their constituencies. These periodicals served to inform movement activists about pertinent actions, news stories, and cultural trends unreported by the mainstream media. The Women's and Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender (LGBT) Periodicals Collection comprises individual issues of periodicals produced by or reporting on organizations involved in the women's rights and lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender rights movements of the late twentieth century and early twenty-first century. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
98 boxes
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The periodicals in the Women's and Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Movements (LGBT) Periodicals Collection were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a series of gifts and purchases from 2006-2016.
Historical Note
Since the 1960s, and particularly after the Stonewall uprising of 1969, the modern women's rights and lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender rights movements have produced their own magazines, journals, newspapers, and newsletters as a strategy for unifying and galvanizing their constituencies. These periodicals served to inform movement activists about pertinent actions, news stories, and cultural trends unreported by the mainstream media. Owing to the high cost of periodicals publication and the demands of time and staff required, these publications—many produced by resource-poor organizations in major U.S. cities—display a wide variety of production methods; many periodicals were published only for brief periods of time.
Collection Overview
The collection comprises individual issues of periodicals produced by or reporting on organizations involved in the women's rights and lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender rights movements (LGBT) of the late twentieth century and early twenty-first century. A wide variety of periodical genres are represented here, including literary and art journals, newspapers, organizational newsletters, and popular culture magazines. The periodicals in this collection were donated by individuals, purchased, or separated from manuscript collections. Manuscript collections held by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library from which periodicals were separated are the Catherine Nicholson Papers; the Dan Kirsch Papers; the Kate Millett Papers; the Irene Peslikis Papers; the Minnie Bruce Pratt Papers; the Margaret McFadden Papers; and the Charis Books and More-Charis Circle Records. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
The original collection numbered forty-one boxes. Additions in 2009, 2011 and 2012 expanded the collection.
Related Material
Charis Books and More-Charis Circle records, 1976-2006.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Dan Kirsch papers, 1975-2004.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Margaret McFadden papers, [1970s]-2005 and undated.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Kate Millett papers, 1912-2002 and undated.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Catherine Nicholson papers, 1942-2005 and undated.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Irene Peslikis papers, 1957-2002 and undated.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Minnie Bruce Pratt papers, 1870s-2005 and undated.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Feminism -- United States -- Periodicals; Feminism and art; Feminism -- Political aspects -- United States; Feminism -- United States; Gay activists -- United States; Gay community -- United States; Feminism and art -- United States -- Periodicals; Feminist theory -- United States -- Periodicals; Women's periodicals, American; Women political activists -- United States; Lesbian feminism -- United States; Lesbian culture -- United States; Transgender people -- Social conditions -- United States; Lesbian feminist theory -- United States; Gay culture -- United States; Gay liberation movement -- United States -- Periodicals; Lesbian activists -- United States; Lesbian community -- United States; Pratt, Minnie Bruce; Peslikis, Irene; Kirsch, Dan; McFadden, Margaret; Millett, Kate; Nicholson, Catherine; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture; Charis Books and More
- Women's and Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Movements (LGBT) Periodicals Collection, 1968-2005, 41 boxes
  - Sinister Wisdom, no. 16-19, 28, 36-42, 48-49, 53, 57 (Box 1)
  - Trivia, no. 1-13, 16/17, 20 (Box 2)
  - women, Vol. 1, no. 2; Vol. 4, no. 1,3,4; Vol. 5, no. 1-3; Vol. 8, no. 1,2 (Box 2)
  - Women, Vol. 6, no. 2,3; Vol. 7, no. 1-3 (Box 3)
  - Sisters, Vol. 2, no. 1,11; Feb. 1972; Vol. 3, no. 9,10; Dec. 1972-Feb. 1973; Vol. 4, no. 3,7,8,12; April 1973; Nov. 1973; Vol. 5, no. 1-12; Vol. 6, no. 1-2 (Box 3)
  - Focus, Vol. 2, no. 12; Vol. 3, no. 1; Sept. 1972; Nov. 1972; Jan.-Jun. 1973; Sept.-Dec. 1973; Feb. 1974; Apr.-Dec. 1974 (Box 3)
  - Focus, Jan.-Mar. 1975; May-Dec. 1975; Jan.-Dec. 1976; Jan.-Dec. 1977; Jan.-Nov. 1978; Dec./Jan.-Jun./Jul. 1979; Sept./Oct.-Nov./Dec. 1979; 1979; Jan./Feb.-Nov./Dec. 1980; Jan./Feb. 1981; May/Jun. 1981; Jan./ Feb. 1982; Sept./Oct. 1982 (Box 4)
  - Muthah, undated (1 issue) (Box 4)
  - In Your Face, Spring 1995 (Box 4)
  - Awakening: A Womyn's Reality, vol. 2 (Jan./Feb. 1988) (Box 4)
  - Writing on the Wall, Summer 1989 (Box 4)
  - The Lesbian News, Vol. 12, no. 7 (Box 4)
  - Hashte Mars, no. 12-14 (Box 4)
  - Bitch: The Women's Rock Newsletter with Bite, no. 4, 10-11, 21-22 (Box 4)
  - Bitch: The Women's Rock Mag with Bite, no. 18-20 (Box 4)
  - Hot Wire, Vol. 5, no. 2 (Box 4)
  - Women, Summer 1970; Vol. 2, no. 3; Winter 1971; Vol. 3, no. 3-4; Vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 5)
  - Redstockings, 1990-1991 (1 issue) (Box 5)
  - Vision, Vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 5)
  - Off Our Backs, Vol. II, no. 7 (Box 5)
  - Craft Horizons, Vol. XXX, no. 6 (Box 5)
  - Left Curve, no. 3 (Box 5)
  - The Fox, no. 1-2 (Box 5)
  - Chalk Circle, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 5)
  - Feminist Art Journal, Spring 1974 (Box 5)
  - Woman Space, Vol. 1, no. 1,2 (Box 5)
  - Everywoman, Vol. 2, no. 7 (Box 5)
  - New Directions for Women, Vol. 7, no. 3, 4; Vol. 8, no. 1, 3, 5; Vol. 9, no. 1-3 (Box 5)
  - Artworkers News, Vol. 8, no. 1 (Box 6)
  - Seven Days, Vol. 1, no. 1; Vol. 2, no. 7 (Box 6)
  - Feminist Art Journal, Vol. 1, no. 2; Vol. 2, no. 1, 3, 4; Vol. 3, no. 2, 4; Vol. 4, no. 2, Vol. 5, no. 1 (Box 6)
  - Womanart, Vol. 1, no. 3; Vol. 2, no. 3 (Box 6)
  - Art Journal, Vol. 43, no. 3 (Box 6)
  - Cuba Resource Center Newsletter, Vol. 2, no. 2 (Box 6)
  - Women Artists News, Vol. 6, no. 6&7 (Box 6)
  - The Spokeswoman, Vol. 1, no. 11 (Box 6)
  - New York, Vol. 3, no. 20 (Box 6)
  - New York, Vol. 4, no. 51 (Box 6)
  - Battle Acts, Vol. 1, no. 4 (Box 6)
  - Velvet Glove, no. 6 (Feb-Mar 1972) (Box 6)
  - The Atlantic, Vol. 227, no. 5 (Box 6)
  - Motive, Vol. 29, no. 6/7 (Box 6)
  - Quadrille, Vol. 2, no. 5 (Box 6)
  - Motive, Vol. 32, no. 2 (Box 6)
  - Mademoiselle, Vol. 70, no. 4 (Box 6)
  - Up from under, Vol. 1, no. 2, 4 (Box 6)
  - Fusion, no. 46 (Box 7)
  - Women & Art, Summer/Fall 1972 (Box 7)
  - Liberation, Vol. 15, no. 2 (Box 7)
  - Women's Liberation, no. 23 (Box 7)
  - RAT Subterranean News, Vol. 2, no. 27, 28; June 1970 (Box 7)
  - Militant, Vol. 33, no. 43, 45, 48; Vol. 34, no. 1,5 (Box 7)
  - Guardian, Vol. 21, no. 22-24; Vol. 22, no. 19 (Box 7)
  - Majority Report, Vol. 7, no. 9-14, 19; Vol. 8, no. 10 (Box 7)
  - Sapphic Touch, no. 1 (Box 7)
  - New Dawn for Women, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 7)
  - Time Canada, Vol. 99, no. 12 (Box 7)
  - Working Woman, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 7)
  - Feminist Bookstore News, Vol. 17, no. 1, 5; Vol. 18, no. 5, 6; Vol. 19, no. 1, 3, 4; Vol. 20, no. 2-4; Vol. 21, no. 1-4; Vol. 22, no. 3/4 (Box 8)
  - Other Side, Vol. 17, no. 3-12; Vol. 18, no. 2, 3 (Box 8)
  - Matrix, Vol. 1, no. 6-11; Vol. 2, no. 1-9, 11; Vol. 3, no. 1-10, 12-14; Vol. 4, no. 3-5, 7, 9-12; Vol. 5, no. 2, 4-8, 10 (Box 9)
  - Sinister Wisdom, no. 21, 22/23, 24-27, 31-32, 34, 47, 54 (Box 10)
  - Woman of Power, no. 7-11 (Box 10)
  - Women, Vol. 6, no. 1 (Box 10)
  - Heresies, Vol. 1, no. 1-2; Vol. 4, no. 4 (Box 10)
  - Heresies, Vol. 5, no. 2; Vol. 6, no. 3-4 (Box 11)
  - The Lesbian Feminist, Sept./Oct. 1976; Feb. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Prime Time, Vol. 1, no. 13-14 (Box 11)
  - Pointblank Times, Vol. 1, no. 3-9; Vol. 2, no. 2 (Box 11)
  - The Brown Papers, Vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 11)
  - Society for Human Abortion, Inc. Newsletter, Vol. 6, no. 3 (Box 11)
  - Santa Cruz Women's Health Center Newsletter, no. 8-12, 18 (Box 11)
  - The Wree-View, Fall 1976; May/Jun.-Jul./Aug. 1977; Jan./Feb.-May/Jun. 1978; Vol. 4, no. 1-3; Vol. 5, no. 1-2, 3/4, 5; Vol. 6, no. 1-3, 3/4 (Box 11)
  - Sisters Stand, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 11)
  - Tell-a-Woman, Vol. 3, no. 8-9; Vol. 4, no. 3, 6-8; Vol. 5, no. 3, 7; Vol. 8, no. 1; Vol. 9, no. 9 (Box 11)
  - WIA Newsletter, Vol. 1, no. 9-11; Vol. 2, no. 1-4, 6; Vol. 4, no. 1-9 (Box 11)
  - Sister, Vol. 4, no. 6; Vol. 5, no. 5, 7-8; Vol. 6, no. 6, 8-9, 11-12; Vol. 7, no. 2; Vol. 8, no. 1; Vol. 9, no. 1 (Box 11)
  - Sassy, Vol. 2, no. 9; Vol. 3, no. 12-13; Vol. 4, no. 1, 11-12; Vol. 5, no. 1, 4-5 (Box 12)
  - Off Our Backs, Vol. 1, no. 20; Vol. 3, no. 9; Jul. 1974; Vol. 10, no. 2; Vol. 15, no. 1, 3-5, 7, 10-11; Vol. 16, no. 1-4, 6, 8; Vol. 17, no. 3, 5 (Box 12)
  - Spinning Off, Feb. 1978; Vol. 1, no. 2; Vol. 2, no. 12, 14-16; Aug. 1979; Sept. 1979; Vol. 2, no. 17-19; Oct. 1980; Dec. 1980 (Box 12)
  - Atalanta, Vol. 6, no. 6, 8-9; Vol. 7, no. 1-3 (Box 12)
  - Wommin Together, Mar. 1984 (Box 13)
  - Scarlet Women, no. 10 (Box 13)
  - Out and About, Sept. 1979 (Box 13)
  - We Ain't Got it Easy but... We Got It!, Vol. 1, no. 6; Vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 13)
  - Brown Sister, no. 4 (Box 13)
  - So's Your Old Lady, no. 13 (Box 13)
  - North Carolinians United for ERA, Vol. 1, no. 1-2, 4-5 (Box 13)
  - Women and Revolution, no. 32-33 (Box 13)
  - Womanews, Vol. 7, no. 4 (Box 13)
  - No More Cages, Vol. 5, no. 5 (Box 13)
  - Au Courant, Vol. 7, no. 15 (Box 13)
  - Girlfriends, Vol. 5, no. 7-8; Oct. 1998; Vol. 5, no. 11; Vol. 6, no. 5, 9-10 (Box 13)
  - Kinesis, Nov. 1993; Dec. 1993/Jan. 1994; Mar. 1994 (Box 13)
  - Cuba Review, Vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 13)
  - National NOW Times, Vol. 20, no. 5-6; Vol. 21, no. 1; Vol. 26, no. 1-3; Vol. 27, no. 1, 4-6 (Box 13)
  - Off Our Backs, Vol. 4, no. 4; Vol. 15, no. 2, 6, 8-9; Vol. 16, no. 5, 7, 9-11; Vol. 17, no. 1-2, 10-11; Vol. 18, no. 1-11; Vol. 19, no. 1-10 (Box 14)
  - Off Our Backs, Vol. 20, no. 1-2, 9-10; Vol. 21, no. 2, 4-7, 9-11; Vol. 22, no. 1-4, 6-10; Vol. 23, no. 1-2, 5-9, 11; Vol. 24, no. 1-2, 4, 10-11 (Box 15)
  - Off Our Backs, Vol. 25, no. 1-11; Vol. 26, no. 4-6, 9; Vol. 27, no. 8; Vol. 29, no. 10-11 (Box 16)
  - Women and Art, Winter 1971 (Box 16)
  - Women, Fall 1970 (Box 16)
  - Woman's Art Journal, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 16)
  - Quest, Vol. 1, no. 1-4; Vol. 2, no. 1-4; Vol. 3, no. 1-3; Vol. 4, no. 1-4 (Box 16)
  - Conditions, no. 1, 3-10, 11/12, 13, 15-17 (Box 17)
  - Common Lives, Lesbian Lives, no. 36 (Box 17)
  - Socialist Review, Vol. 22, no. 1 (Box 17)
  - Feminist Art Journal, Vol. 4, no. 1 (Box 17)
  - Sojourner, Vol. 3, no. 7-8, 11-12; Vol. 4, no. 1, 3, 10 (Box 18)
  - Spectre, no. 3-4 (Box 18)
  - Ain't I a Woman?, Vol. 1, no. 10, 17; Vol. 3, nos 1, 4 (Box 18)
  - Majority Report, Vol. 9, no. 9 (Box 18)
  - Women & Film, Vol. 1, no. 1; Vol. 2, no. 7 (Box 18)
  - Spokeswoman, Vol. 9, no. 7/8 (Box 18)
  - Country Women, Vol. 1, no. 4-5 (Box 18)
  - MAW, Vol. 1, no. 1-2 (Box 18)
  - Second Wave, Vol. 3, no. 3-4; Vol. 4, no. 1-4; Vol. 5, no. 1 (Box 18)
  - Visibilities, Vol. 2, no. 4 (Box 18)
  - Ms., Spring 1972 (Box 18)
  - Evergreen Chronicles, Vol. 9, no. 1-2 (Box 18)
  - Lesbian Ethics, Vol. 1, no. 1-3; Vol. 2, no. 1-3; Vol. 3, no. 1-3; Vol. 4, no. 1-3 (Box 19)
  - Bridges, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 19)
  - Sinister Wisdom, no. 1-2, 4-15, 43/44 (Box 19)
  - Azalea, Vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 20)
  - Common Lives, Lesbian Lives, no. 22, 32-34, 37 (Box 20)
  - Outlook, Vol. 1, no. 1-4 (Box 20)
  - Aphra, Vol. 4, no. 3 (Box 20)
  - IKON, Vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 20)
  - Feminist Connection, Vol. 2, no. 10 (Box 20)
  - Women Against Pornography Newsreport, Vol. 6, no. 1 (Box 20)
  - New Moon, Vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 20)
  - Lesbian Connection, Vol. 1, no 1/2; Vol. 11, no. 2, 6 (Box 20)
  - Lesbian Tide, Vol. 8, no. 4 (Box 20)
  - Spare Rib, no. 62, 136 (Box 20)
  - Front Page, Vol. 12, no. 2; Vol. 13, no. 22; Vol. 14, no. 16; Vol. 15, no. 3, 7, 10, 12 (Box 20)
  - Q Notes, Vol. 6, no. 2, 4; Vol. 9, no. 16; Vol. 14, no. 19, 22; Vol. 15, no. 10, 18; Vol. 16, no. 8; Vol. 17, no. 6, 11 (Box 21)
  - Charlotte Free Press, Vol. 1, no. 7; Vol. 2, no. 10-26; Vol. 3, no. 1-8 (Box 21)
  - Lezzie-Fair, Jun. 1985 (Box 21)
  - Gay Community News, Vol. 12, no. 39 (Box 21)
  - WIN, Vol. 11, no. 22 (Box 21)
  - Country Women, no. 33 (Box 21)
  - Pointblank Times, Vol. 1, no. 5-7, 9; Vol. 2, no. 1; Vol. 3, no. 5; Vol. 4, no. 1-2 (Box 22)
  - Amazon Quarterly, Vol. 1/2, no. 4/1 (Box 22)
  - Paid My Dues, Vol. 2, no. 4 (Box 22)
  - Woman of Power, no. 1-6, 12-13, 18-20 (Box 22)
  - Chrysalis, no. 1-2, 10 (Box 22)
  - Lesbian Tide, Vol. 5, no. 3-5; Vol. 6, no. 1-6; Vol. 7, no. 1-3 (Box 23)
  - Velvet Park, Vol. 1, no. 1, 3-7 (Box 23)
  - Country Women, no. 17, 27-29, 32 (Box 23)
  - So's Your Old Lady, no. 1-4; Vol. 2, no. 1; no. 10, 19-20 (Box 23)
  - Flaming Faggot, Spring 2003; Winter 2003; Summer 2004 (Box 23)
  - Q Notes, Apr.-Dec. 1989; Jan.-Dec. 1990; Vol. 6, no. 1-12; Vol. 7, no. 1-3, 5-12 (Box 24)
  - Q Notes, Vol. 8, no. 1-12; Vol. 9, no. 1-8, 10-16 (Box 25)
  - Q Notes, Vol. 9, no. 17; Vol. 10, no. 1-4, 6-12; Vol. 11, no. 1-15 (Box 26)
  - Q Notes, Vol. 11, no. 16-25; Vol. 12, no. 1-9, 11-15 (Box 27)
  - Q Notes, Vol. 12, no. 16-26; Vol. 13, no. 2-3, 5-13, 15-17 (Box 28)
  - Q Notes, Vol. 13, no. 18-26; Vol. 14, no. 1-20 (Box 29)
  - Q Notes, Vol. 14, no. 21-25; Vol. 15, no. 1-25 (Box 30)
  - Q Notes, Vol. 15, no. 26; Vol. 16, no. 1-18, 22-26 (Box 31)
  - Q Notes, Vol. 17, no. 1-11, 13-18, 24, 26 (Box 32)
    Scope and Contents note
    Two issues (August 31, 2002 and September 14, 2002) are numbered Vol. 17, no. 8.
  - Q Notes, Vol. 18, no. 1-8, 10-20, 22-26 (Box 33)
  - Q Notes, Vol. 19, no. 1-7, 9-16 (Box 34)
  - Velvet Park, Vol. 1, no. 8-9 (Box 34)
  - Friendly Woman, Vol. 11, no. 6-7 (Box 34)
  - Mountain Astrologer, no. 492 (Box 34)
  - NOW: Hate Crimes Against Lesbians, Sept. 1992 (Box 34)
  - Broomstick, Vol. 15, no. 4 (Box 34)
  - Women's Press, Vol. 2, no. 2-4; Vol. 3, no. 7; Vol. 4, no. 5-6; Vol. 5, no. 1-2, 6-8; Vol. 6, no. 1-5; Vol. 7, no. 1-6; Vol. 8, no. 1-3; Vol. 9, no. 1-4; Vol. 10, no. 2-5; Vol. 11, no. 1, 4 (Box 35)
  - Calyx, Vol. 9, no. 1; Vol. 10, no. 2/3; Vol. 13, no. 3 (Box 36)
  - Room of One's Own, Vol. 19, no. 1 (Box 36)
  - Primavera, Vol. 3 (Box 36)
  - Moving Out, Vol. 5, no. 1-2; Vol. 6, no. 1-2; Vol. 7, no. 1; Vol. 7/8, no. 1/2 (Box 36)
  - Push, Vol. 1, no. 4 (Box 36)
  - Florida NOW Times, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 36)
  - Wichita NOW Times, Vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 36)
  - Synapse, Spring 1994 (Box 36)
  - National NOW Times, Vol. 13, no. 10/11, 12/1; Vol. 14, no. 2-3, 8-9; Vol. 15, no. 2-8, 9/10 (Box 36)
  - National NOW Times, Vol. 16, no. 3-4, 7-9; Vol. 17, no. 1-2, 4-5; Vol. 18, no. 7; Vol. 19, no. 3-6; Vol. 20, no. 1-6; Vol. 21, no. 2-6; Vol. 22, no. 1-6; Vol. 23, no. 1-5; Vol. 24, no. 1-6; Vol. 25, no. 1-5; Vol. 26, no. 1, 3 (Box 37)
  - The Newsletter, Vol. 3, no. 2-3, 15; Vol. 14, no. 8-12; Vol. 15, no. 9-12; Vol. 16, no. 1, 3-4, 6-8, 10-12; Vol. 17, no. 1-12; Vol. 18, no. 1-11; Vol. 19, no. 1-12; Vol. 20, no. 1-4 (Box 38)
  - The Woman Activist, Vol. 1, no. 10-11, 13; Vol. 2, no. 1, 3, 10, 12; Vol. 3, no. 4, 8; Vol. 4, no. 4-5, 8-12; Vol. 5, no. 1-4, 6-11; Vol. 6, no. 1-2, 4-7, 9-13; Vol. 7, no. 2-11; Vol. 8, no. 1, 3-5, 7-11; Vol. 9, no. 1-6, 8, 10; Vol. 10, no. 7; Vol. 11, no. 4 (Box 38)
  - New Directions for Women, Vol. 2, no. 1; Vol. 3, no. 1-4; Vol. 4, no. 1-4; Vol. 5, no. 1-4; Vol. 6, no. 1-4; Vol. 7, no. 1-4; Vol. 8, no. 1-5; Vol. 9, no. 1-6; Vol. 10, no. 1-6; Vol. 11, no. 3-6 (Box 39)
  - Everywoman, Vol. 1, no. 1-11; Vol. 2, no. 15; Vol. 3, no. 1, 30-31 (Box 40)
  - Siren, ca. 1973 (Box 40)
  - Voice of the Women's Liberation Movement, no. 5-7 (Box 40)
  - WomenSports, Vol. 1, no. 3 (Box 40)
  - The Radical Teacher, no. 2 (Box 40)
  - Velvet Fist, Vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 40)
  - Off Our Backs, Vol. 1, no. 2, 24; Vol. 3, no. 3, 5; Vol. 4, no. 1-4, 6, 8-10, 12 (Box 40)
  - Mother, Vol. 1, no. 3, 5-6 (Box 41)
  - Country Women, no. 13 (Box 41)
  - Goodbye to All That, no. 36-37 (Box 41)
  - Health Rights News, Vol. 4, no. 6; Vol. 7, no. 3 (Box 41)
  - Northwest Passage, Vol. 8, no. 7; Vol. 10, no. 6 (Box 41)
  - The Pedestal, Vol. 2, no. 2; Vol. 4, no. 5 (Box 41)
- Addition, 2009
  - Ache, Vol. 1, no. 5, 7; Vol. 3, no. 5; Vol. 4, no. 1-3 (Box 42)
  - Alone Together, nn (Box 42)
  - Las Amantes de La Luna, no. 2-3, 5 (Box 42)
  - Amazon Quarterly, Vol. 1, no. 1; Vol. 2, no. 2-4; Vol. 3, no. 1 (Box 42)
  - The American Sunbather, no. 8 (Box 42)
  - Amethyst, no. 13; 1987 Spring (Box 42)
  - Anything That Moves, no. 5 (Box 42)
  - Astraea, 1992; 1994 (Box 42)
  - Astraea Bulletin, 1993 Winter (Box 42)
  - Atalanta, Vol. 7, no. 4-12; Vol. 8, no. 1-2 (Box 42)
  - Aurora, Vol. 2, no. 1; Vol. 9, no.1 (Box 42)
  - Avanti, Vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 42)
  - Azalea, Vol. 4, no. 1 (Box 42)
  - Battle Acts, Vol. 2, no. 3 (Box 42)
  - Bay Area Career Women, Vol. 16, no. 6; Vol. 17, no. 1-2, 8-11; Vol. 18, no. 7-9; Vol. 19, no. 1-2, 4, 6-11; Vol. 20, no. 1, 3-5, 7-8; Vol. 21, no. 1-3, 5-6, 8, 12; Vol. 22, no. 1, 4 (Box 43)
  - Bay Area Feminist Federal Credit Union (BAFFCU) Bulletin, 1979 October (Box 43)
  - Belles Lettres, Vol. 3, no. 3 (Box 43)
  - Big, 1965 Summer, December (Box 43)
  - Big Apple Dyke News, Vol. 4, no. 1 (Box 43)
  - The Big Boys, 1965 September (Box 43)
  - Black Maria, Vol. 3, no. 2-3; Vol. 4, no. 2-3 (Box 43)
  - The Blatant Image, no. 1 (Box 43)
  - Body, Vol. 1, no. 1, 4; Vol. 2, no. 6 (Box 43)
  - The Body Politic, no. 14-15, 18 (Box 43)
  - The Bond, Vol. 6, no. 3 (Box 43)
  - Boy Friends, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 43)
  - Cahiers du Feminisme, no. 19 (Box 44)
  - Les Cahiers du Grif: Femmes entre elles, 1978 April (Box 44)
  - Calyx, Vol. 1, no. 16; Vol. 3, no. 3; Vol. 4, no. 1-3; Vol. 5, no. 1-3; Vol. 6, no. 1-2; Vol. 7, no. 2-3; Vol. 8, no. 1-3; Vol. 10, no. 1; Vol. 11, no. 1-3 (Box 44)
  - Calyx, Vol. 12, no. 1-3; Vol. 13, no. 1-2; Vol. 14, no. 1-3; Vol. 15, no. 1-2; Vol. 16, no. 2-3; Vol. 17, no. 1; Vol. 18, no. 2-3 (Box 45)
  - Calyx, Vol. 19, no. 2-3; Vol. 20, no. 1-3; Vol. 21, no. 3 (Box 46)
  - Changing Men, no. 24 (Box 46)
  - Charlotte Free Press, Vol. 1, no. 1-2, 4-5 (Box 46)
  - Chrysalis, no. 3, 7, 9 (Box 46)
  - Ciao!, Vol. 1, no. 1-4, 6; Vol. 2, no. 1-2; Vol. 3, no. 1 (Box 46)
  - Citoyennes, no. 38 (Box 47)
  - Communist, no. 5 (Box 47)
  - Coq d'Or (The Golden Cock), Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 47)
  - Country Women, Vol. 1, no. 3; 6-10, 14, 18, 26, 31 (Box 47)
  - Cowrie, Vol. 2, no. 2 (Box 47)
  - Coyote Howls, Vol. 4, no. 1; Vol. 5, no. 1 (Box 47)
  - Davka, Vol. 1, no. 1-3 (Box 47)
  - Deneuve, Vol. 4, no. 5; Vol. 5, no.3 (Box 47)
  - Des Femmes, no. 1-5, 7-13 (Box 47)
  - Des Femmes Hebdo, no. 1-4, 6-26, 39, 41-43, 50, 55/56, 60, 63-66; 75-88 (Box 48)
  - Desire, 2004 Preview, Summer, Fall (Box 48)
  - Desormais, no. 1-8 (Box 48)
  - Dilettante, Vol. 1, no. 1-4 (Box 49)
  - Dinah, 1995 Sept/Oct, Nov/Dec (Box 49)
  - Discovery, no. 2 (Box 49)
  - Double-F, no. 5 (Box 49)
  - Drum, Vol. 4, no. 9; Vol. 5, no. 11 (Box 49)
  - Dyke Digest, Vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 49)
  - Dykes and Gorgons, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 49)
  - Effe, Vol. 1, no. 1-2; Vol. 3, no. 1-5, 9-11; Vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 49)
  - Emma, 1985 March; [1991 Feb]; 1992 Jan, March (Box 49)
  - L'erba Voglio, Vol. 5, no. 18/19 (Box 49)
  - Feelings, no. 1 (Box 49)
  - Fem., Vol. 1, no. 4; Vol. 2, no. 5; Vol. 8, no. 36 (Box 49)
  - Feminist Bookstore News, Vol. 16, no. 4, 9; Vol. 18, no. 1, 3; Vol. 19, no. 6; Vol. 20, no. 5/6; Vol. 21, no. 5-6; Vol. 22, no. 1-4, 6; 1990 Aug; 1995 Aug (Box 50)
  - Fizeek Art Quarterly, no. 13 (Box 51)
  - Focus, 1972 Jan/Feb; 1981 Mar/Apr, Sept/Oct, Nov/Dec; 1982 Mar/Apr, May/June, Jul/Aug, Nov/Dec; 1983 Mar/Apr, May/June, Aug, Dec (Box 51)
  - FPS: A Magazine of Young People's Liberation, no. 49 (Box 51)
  - The Freedom Socialist, Vol. 12, no. 1 (Box 51)
  - Frighten the Horses, no. 9, 12 (Box 51)
  - From Lammas: The Little Review, no. 1-2 (Box 51)
  - Fuor!, no. 1-9; Vol 2., no. 10-11; Vol. 3, no. 12-13; Vol. 4, no. 14 (Box 51)
  - The Gay Alternative, no. 2-7 (Box 52)
  - Gay Community News, Vol. 15, no. 13 (Box 52)
  - Girl Jock, no. 5, 8, 13, 16 (Box 52)
  - Girlfriends, 1994 July; Vol. 1, no. 2; Vol. 2, no. 1-3, 5-6; Vol. 3, no. 1-4, 6; Vol. 4, no. 1-7; Vol. 5, no. 1-6, 9; Vol. 6, no. 1-3, 6, 8 (Box 52)
  - Girlfriends, Vol. 6, no. 11-12; Vol. 7, no. 1, 7; Vol. 8, no. 1 (Box 53)
  - Girls Like Us, no. 1 (Box 53)
  - Great Guys, nn. (Box 53)
  - Grecian Guild Pictorial, no. 52 (Box 53)
  - Grecian Guild Studio Quarterly, no. 11, 13/14 (Box 53)
  - The Greyhuff Review, no. 1-2, 4 (Box 53)
  - Hag Rag, Vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 53)
  - Hasha, 1994 Summer (Box 53)
  - Heavenly Bodies, no. 1 (Box 53)
  - Heresies, no. 5, 9, 17-19 (Box 53)
  - Histoires d'elles, no. 5 (Box 53)
  - The Hot Seat, no. 25 (Box 53)
  - Hot Wire, Vol. 2, no. 2; Vol. 3, no. 3; Vol. 5, no. 3; Vol. 6, no. 2; Vol. 7, no. 1-3; Vol. 8, no. 1 (Box 53)
  - Hot Wire, Vol. 8, no. 2-3; Vol. 9, no. 1-3; Vol. 10, no. 1-3 (Box 54)
  - Hues, Vol. 1, no. 6; Vol. 2, no. 1; Vol. 3, no. 1; Vol. 4, no. 1, 3-5; Vol. 5, no. 1-2 (Box 54)
  - IKON, Vol. 2, no. 2, 7-8 (Box 54)
  - International Nudist Sun, no. 1, 4 (Box 54)
  - Issues! The Magazine for Lesbians of Color, Vol. 1, no. 3 (Box 54)
  - The James White Review, Vol. 1, no. 1, 4 (Box 54)
  - Jane and Jane: The Home and Family Magazine, Vol. 1, no. 1-2 (Box 54)
  - Jr., Vol. 3, no. 2; Vol. 11, no. 6 (Box 54)
  - The Kansas City Woman, Vol. 1, no. 4-5 (Box 55)
  - The Ladder, Vol. 1, no. 7; Vol. 2, no. 9; Vol. 16, no. 1/2 (Box 55)
  - Lambda: The Carolina Gay and Lesbian Association Newsletter, Vol. 15, no. 2-3 (Box 55)
  - Lambda Book Report, Vol. 5, no. 1 (Box 55)
  - ΛΕΣΒΙΑ (Lambda Epsilon Sigma Beta Iota Alpha) International Women's News Vol. 1, no. 3 (Box 55)
  - Lance, no. 2 (Box 55)
  - Lavendar Woman, Vol. 4, no. 5 (Box 55)
  - Leap Leap: Shameless Hussy Review, no. 5 (Box 55)
  - The Leaping Lesbian, Vol. 3, no. 2 (Box 55)
  - Le'sbeinformed, 1978 Dec (Box 55)
  - Lesbia Magazine, no. 158-163, 165, 167-168, 170-179, 181, 183-191 (Box 55)
  - Lesbia Magazine, no. 192-199, 202-208, 211-212, 219, 229-230, 234, 239, 242, 244-246 (Box 56)
  - Lesbian Connection, Vol. 4, no. 3; Vol. 16, no. 3, 6; Vol. 17, no. 2, 4-6; Vol. 18, no. 1-5; Vol. 19, no. 1, 3; Vol. 20, no. 6; Vol. 21, no. 1-6; Vol. 22, no. 1-5 (Box 56)
  - Lesbian Connection, Vol. 22, no. 6; Vol. 23, no. 1-6; Vol. 24, no. 1-6; Vol. 25, no. 1, 3-6; Vol. 26, no. 1-3, 5-6; Vol. 27, no. 2-5 (Box 57)